rocketmill.co.uk 2014-02-13

# Privacy Policy - RocketMill

## How RocketMill Handles Private/Personal Information

Our **privacy policy** defines how RocketMill uses and protects all information that you give RocketMill when you use our website.

We are determined to ensure that **your privacy is protected**. If you provide certain information by which you could be identified when using our website we assure you that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

We may change the detail of this policy sporadically. Please check this page to make sure you are satisfied with our policy when you return to the site in future. This policy is effective from October 2010.

### Information we retain

We might collect and keep the following information:

  * Name and job title
  * Contact information including email address
  * Demographic information such as postcode
  * Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

### What we do with the information

This information helps us understand your needs and provide a better response/service. Below is why we may keep the aforementioned data:

  * Internal records
  * To improve our products and services
  * To contact you regarding your enquiry

### We do not:

  * Sell, lease or distribute your data to third parties.

### Security

We are committed to handling your information in a secure fashion. We safeguard your data by implementing suitable electronic and physical measures.

### Links to other websites

We may place links to other websites within our site. Should you follow these links we are not responsible and cannot control what these websites do with information you submit there. Controlling your personal information.

### Personal Information

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee may be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to: **RocketMill Ltd, Basepoint Innovation Centre, Metcalf Way, Crawley, West Sussex, RH11 7XX**.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
